{"id":"2018_3","name":"","memoryVerse":"\"The commander of the Lord's army replied, 'Take off your sandals, for the place where you are standing is holy.' And Joshua did so.\" â€“ Joshua 5:15","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2018_3_1","questionText":"1. Use this space to record how you have seen God's activity during the week. (How has He provided, answered, comforted, reconciled, guided, etc.?)","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_3_2","questionText":"2. What from the notes, lecture, group sharing or personal study impacted you most in the past week?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read Joshua 10:1-15.","readVerse":[{"book":"Joshua","verse":"10:1-15"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_3_3","questionText":"3. How did Joshua respond to the new challenge he faced? How did God encourage him?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_3_4","questionText":"4. What did God do supernaturally for Joshua and the Israelite army? What do these verses reveal about God?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_3_5","questionText":"5. What principles about integrity and prayer can you draw from these verses?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read Joshua 10:16-43.","readVerse":[{"book":"Joshua","verse":"10:16-43"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_3_6","questionText":"6. What was the reaction of the surrounding Canaanites after Joshua's armies returned from routing the armies of the five cities? What was the reason for it?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_3_7","questionText":"7. What did Joshua tell his men to do when they brought the five kings to him? What does this total victory point toward? (For help, see Psalm 110:1; Romans 16:20; 1 Corinthians 15:24-27 and any other Bible passages.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"110:1"},{"book":"Romans","verse":"16:20"},{"book":"1 Corinthians","verse":"15:24-27"}]},{"id":"2018_3_8","questionText":"8. How does the reality that God fights for His people encourage you as you fight against discouragement, temptation, worry, etc.?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read Joshua 11.","readVerse":[{"book":"Joshua","verse":"11:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_3_9","questionText":"9. What command and promise did the Lord give Joshua as a large number of kings joined forces to fight Israel? What does it tell you about Joshua, his enemies and God?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_3_10","questionText":"10. What was the significance of the destruction of the Anakites? (See Numbers 13:21-14:9; Deuteronomy 9:1-5 for help.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Numbers","verse":"13:21-14:9"},{"book":"Deuteronomy","verse":"9:1-5"}]},{"id":"2018_3_11","questionText":"11. What questions or doubts have you struggled with as you read these chapters describing violence and destruction?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read Joshua 12.","readVerse":[{"book":"Joshua","verse":"12:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_3_12","questionText":"12. Why would God include this list of defeated kings in the Bible? What does this chapter reveal about God's word, character and promises? (See Genesis 15:18-19; Exodus 23:31-33)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Genesis","verse":"15:18-19"},{"book":"Exodus","verse":"23:31-33"}]},{"id":"2018_3_13","questionText":"13. What inspires you about Joshua?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_3_14","questionText":"14. What habits or practices in your life will you ask God to help you conquer?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review Joshua 10-12.","readVerse":[{"book":"Joshua","verse":"10:1-12:999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_3_15","questionText":"15. Choose one or more verses from this week's lesson, and quietly think deeply (meditate) on what is written. Are you taking these verses to heart and living them? Share with your group what God has revealed to you. People of the Promised Land I Lesson 3 \" www.bsfinternational.org AdQ (06.2018) \" 7 8 \" AdQ (06.2018) www.bsfinternational.org \" People of the Promised Land I Lesson 3","answer":"","quotes":[]}]}}}